{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which Player has won the no. of Man of the Match awards?",
      "correct": "Yuvraj Singh",
      "type": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "What is special about a chameleon?",

      "correct": 0,
      "answers": [
        "It changes color",
        "It can live without food",
        "It has no eyes",
        "It can live without food and has no eyes",
        "It can breath underwater and fly"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Michael Jordan's nicknames?",
      "caption": "Mark all that apply",
      "type": "checkbox",
      "correct": [0, 2, 3],
      "answers": ["Air Jordan", "Black Dog", "Black Cat", "His airness"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the 'e' of e-mail stand for?",
      "caption": "The answer should be written in lowercase",
      "type": "input",
      "correct": "electronic"
    },
    {
      "question": "What animal is called 'the ship of the desert'?",

      "correct": 2,
      "answers": ["Snake", "Coyote", "Camel", "Turtle", "Fox"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What dogs are white with black spots all over them?",

      "correct": 1,
      "answers": ["Huskies", "Dalmatians", "Sheep dog", "Alsations"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does WWW stand for?",

      "correct": 2,
      "answers": [
        "Widened Web World",
        "Wireless Wide Web",
        "World Wide Web",
        "Window Web World"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The name of which shampoo brand is made up of two different parts of the body?",

      "correct": 1,
      "answers": ["Herbal Essence", "Head & Shoulders", "Schauma", "Pantene"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the 'Big Bang Theory' deal with?",

      "correct": 3,
      "answers": ["Medicine", "Human Body", "Music", "Universe"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What word completes the following idiom. 'Easier Said Than...'?",
      "caption": "The answer should be written in lowercase",
      "type": "input",
      "correct": "done"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the acronym NASA stand for?",
      "caption": "Mark all that apply",

      "correct": 2,
      "answers": [
        "National Army and Soldiers Administration",
        "National Art and Sculpture Administration",
        "National Aeronautics and Space Administration",
        "National Airforce and Special Administration"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Complete the commonly used idiom. 'Better late than ...'",
      "caption": "The answer should be written in lowercase",
      "type": "input",
      "correct": "never"
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you want if you send an S.O.S. signal?",

      "correct": 1,
      "answers": ["Back-up", "Help", "Digital Television"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does CD stand for?",

      "correct": 2,
      "answers": [
        "Capacity Disk",
        "Copyable Disk",
        "Compact Disc",
        "Circular Disk"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Joseph Barbera and William Hannah created which cat and mouse duo?",

      "correct": 3,
      "answers": [
        "Mickey and Minnie",
        "James and Jerry",
        "Tom and Mickey",
        "Tom and Jerry"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the shortest month of the year?",

      "correct": 3,
      "answers": ["September", "May", "April", "February"]
    },
    {
      "question": "On which continent would you find the fewest people?",

      "correct": 0,
      "answers": ["Antarctica", "South America", "Africa", "Europe"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Italian great mind, who made improvements to the telescope, is known as the 'father of modern science'?",

      "correct": 1,
      "answers": ["Venturi", "Galileo", "Rubia", "Galvani", "Leonardo da Vinci"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the chemical symbol for 'Germanium'?",

      "correct": 3,
      "answers": ["Be", "Ae", "Ce", "Ge"]
    }
  ]
}
